{
    "subject": "Dudley_Moore",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Tuesday_Weld",
    "human_readable": "Dudley Moore is married to Tuesday Weld.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885556101799011,
            "question": "Is Tuesday Weld married to Dudley Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.985426664352417,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9648656845092773,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9562233686447144,
            "question": "What is the marital connection between Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8873676061630249,
            "question": "To whom is Tuesday Weld married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8850411772727966,
            "question": "Who is Dudley Moore married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8237923979759216,
            "question": "Are Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld romantically involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6842436790466309,
            "question": "Who is associated with the name Tuesday Weld in terms of marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6516342163085938,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Dudley Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6403599977493286,
            "question": "What is the name of Dudley Moore's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dudley Moore is married to Tuesday Weld.",
            "html": "yago_1053_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Dudley Moore?",
            "html": "yago_1053_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is associated with the name Tuesday Weld in terms of marriage?",
            "html": "yago_1053_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld romantically involved?",
            "html": "yago_1053_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1053_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Dudley Moore is married to Tuesday Weld\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The first document mentions that Dudley Moore and Tuesday Weld were married for 4 years, specifying their marriage date and divorce date.\n* The subsequent documents provide further evidence of their relationship by mentioning them as a couple, with one document even referring to them as the \"iconic couple\".\n* Therefore, based on the provided context information, it can be concluded that Dudley Moore was indeed married to Tuesday Weld."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Dudley Moore is married to Tuesday Weld.\" The details include their marriage date, duration of their relationship before and after marriage, and mention of their son."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}